crimecraft.com 2010-04-07

# Privacy Policy - CrimeCraft

**Vogster Entertainment LLC  
**

**Privacy Policy**

**Date Last Modified: May 20, 2009**

Vogster Entertainment LLC, and its subsidiaries and affiliates (“Vogster,” “we” or “us”) respect your privacy and are committed to complying fully with United States laws and regulations regarding online privacy protection, and any information you provide to Vogster via its [www.crimecraft.com](http://www.crimecraft.com/) website (the “Site”) will be treated in accordance with those laws and regulations and as set forth herein this privacy policy (the “Privacy Policy”). Visitors to the Site from outside the United States are advised that this Privacy Policy is intended to meet the laws and requirements of the United States, which may not be the same as the laws and regulations of your home country.

We are providing you with this Privacy Policy in order to inform you of our policies with respect to information collected from visitors to the Site. Your use of the Site constitutes your acceptance of this Privacy Policy and your consent to the practices it describes. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THIS PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT USE THE SITE.

**1\. Automatic Collection of Anonymous Information**

Vogster may collect information including internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks. We collect this information in the form of log files so that we can analyze trends, administer the site, track users’ movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. Log files are not linked to Personally Identifiable Information. Additionally, we may use a tracking utility that uses log files to analyze user movement.

**2\. Personally Identifiable Information**

Personally identifiable information is any information that concerns you individually and would permit someone to contact you, for example, your name, address, telephone/fax number, e-mail address, any credit card information you submit to the site, or any information you submit to the Site that identifies you individually (“Personally Identifiable Information”).

We will not collect any Personally Identifiable Information about you unless you provide it. Therefore, if you do not want Vogster to obtain any Personally Identifiable Information about you, do not submit it.

You can visit and browse the Site without revealing Personally Identifiable Information about yourself. You may also choose to disclose Personally Identifiable Information about yourself, which may be maintained as described below. We may collect Personally Identifiable Information about you through registration forms, which may require you to provide, without limitation, your name, e-mail address, postal address, telephone number, areas of interest, product usage, and/or a unique individual password. Such forms may be required to purchase items from Vogster, to enter a promotion, to become a registered user, or to request information about Vogster and its products and services through another site.

Should you choose to communicate with Vogster through e-mail, via the Site, by telephone, in writing, or through other means, we may collect the information in these communications, and such information may be Personally Identifiable Information.

We may also collect Personally Identifiable Information about you when you make a purchase through the Site. If you would like to correct or delete any Personally Identifiable Information, please contact us at support@crimecraft.com.

**3\. “Cookies”**

The Vogster servers, or the servers of companies that are used to operate the Site, may place a “cookie” on your computer in order to allow you to use the Site and to personalize your experience.

A cookie can be stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Cookies allow us to recognize your computer while you are on the Site and help customize your online experience and make it more convenient for you. Cookies are also useful in allowing more efficient log-in for users, tracking transaction histories and preserving information between sessions. The information collected from cookies may also be used to improve the functionality of the Site and to measure traffic patterns.

Advertisers and/or other content providers that may appear on our Site may also use cookies that are not sent by us. Such advertisements or content may use cookies to help track and target the interests of users of the Site in order to present customized and personalized advertisements or other messages that the user might find interesting. Vogster is not responsible for any such cookies. Please note that most web browser applications (such as Microsoft Internet Explorer and Mozilla Firefox) have features that can notify you when you receive a cookie or prevent cookies from being sent. If you disable cookies, however, you may not be able to use certain personalized functions of the Site.

**4\. Ordering from Vogster**

If you wish to make purchases through the Site you will be asked to provide certain Personally Identifiable Information, such as full name, billing address, e-mail address, phone number, and credit card number and expiration date. Please note that you must be 18 or older to make purchases through the Site.

**5\. Information Use**

Vogster may use Personally Identifiable Information collected through the Site to, among other things, respond to inquiries or comments, to verify the identity of users, to maintain or administer user accounts, to maintain the security and integrity of the Site and its data, to provide support to users, to process transactions, to communicate with users regarding transactions made via the Site, to improve and personalize the Site for user preferences, to provide users with product or service updates, promotional notices, and to offer services and products of interest to users.

Vogster uses the anonymous information collected automatically by our servers primarily to help us administer and improve our Site. We may also use aggregated anonymous information to provide information about our Site to advertisers, potential business partners and other unaffiliated entities. Again, this information is not personally identifiable.

**6\. Disclosure of Information**

We may use unaffiliated companies to help us maintain and operate the Site or for other reasons related to the operation of our business, and those companies may receive your Personally Identifiable Information for that purpose. We may also disclose Personally Identifiable Information about you in connection with legal requirements, such as in response to an authorized subpoena, governmental request or investigation, or as otherwise permitted by law. Finally, we may sell or buy corporate assets, and in such transactions user information may be one of the transferred business assets. If Vogster or certain of its assets are acquired, user information may be transferred.

**7\. Security**

Vogster maintains physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to help guard Personally Identifiable Information. If transactions are offered on the Site, transaction information is transmitted to and from the Site in encrypted form using industry-standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) connections to help protect such information from interception. Vogster restricts authorized access to your personal information to those persons who have a legitimate purpose to know that information to provide products or services to you and those persons you have authorized to have access to such information. Vogster also has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control (e.g., verification of Site user’s identity through username and password). Please be aware, however, that any e-mail or other transmission you send through the internet cannot be completely protected against unauthorized interception, and it is your sole responsibility to protect the secrecy of your password.

**8\. Children's Privacy**

You must be 18 years of age to create an account on [www.crimecraft.com](http://www.crimecraft.com/).

**9\. Opt-Out**

In order to provide services to you, Vogster may send you communications related to your transactions, security, or the administration of the Site. From time to time, Vogster may also wish to send you other messages or updates about Vogster, or its promotions and other activities. If you would prefer not to receive future e-mail communications from Vogster and its affiliates, you may click on a link if provided or you may send an e-mail containing your request to support@crimecraft.com.

**10\. External Links**

This Privacy Policy does not extend to other sites on the Internet that are owned and operated by third party vendors and other third parties to which we may link (“External Sites”). Please be aware that Vogster is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of External Sites. External Sites may use cookies. Vogster encourages you to read the privacy policies provided by External Sites before you provide Personally Identifiable Information to them.

**11\. Severance**

If any of this Privacy Policy is determined to be illegal, invalid or otherwise unenforceable by reason of the laws of any state or country in which this Privacy Policy is intended to be effective, then to the extent and within the jurisdiction in which that term is illegal, invalid or unenforceable, it shall be severed and deleted from this Privacy Policy and the remaining terms of the Privacy Policy shall survive, remain in full force and effect, and continue to be binding and enforceable.

**12\. Governing Law/Jurisdiction**

This Privacy Policy is governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of New Jersey. You agree to submit to the personal jurisdiction of the courts of the State of New Jersey for any cause of action arising out of or relating to this Privacy Policy, and hereby waive any right to participate in any type of law suit brought and/or maintained as a class action or similar in nature to a class action.

**13\. Modifications of this Privacy Policy**

Vogster shall have the right, at its sole discretion, to modify, add or remove any terms or conditions of this Privacy Policy without notice or liability to you. Any changes to the Privacy Policy shall be effective immediately following the posting of any such changes on the Site. Please review this Privacy Policy regularly to ensure you are aware of any changes made by Vogster. Your continued use of the Site after changes are posted means you agree to be legally bound by this Privacy Policy as updated and amended.

**14\. Contacting Us**

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, the information practices of Vogster or your dealings with Vogster, please contact us at support@crimecraft.com.
